♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 20=
(If hatred can keep you alive,)
(I hope you loathe me deeply.)
(This path is too dangerous.)
(I should walk it alone.)
The latest telegram has been decoded.
General Kakeo wants the Feng Mausoleum
Treasure Map in Buddha Head
in three days.
(Get the Treasure Map in three days)
General Kakeo also stressed
this is the final deadline.
Or we will bear the consequences.
Reply immediately.
The key to the Buddha Head,
the kingfisher phoenix crown,
is in our hands.
We'll have the treasure map in no time.
We'll make sure it gets done.
Yes.
Let's go.
Without the Buddha Head in three days,
we will all die.
Governor.
You said you killed Xu You'an?
Governor, this item is proof.
I dare not fake it.
Please reward me with the hundred gold.
This thing alone is not enough.
Once I see the head of Xu You'an,
you'll get your money.
Governor,
I've seen
plenty of double-crossing tricks.
I need to see the money first.
Nowadays...
Cut the crap. Lead the way.
Please, Governor.
Please.
(Xu Fan,)
(this hundred gold will be your toll
on the way to the underworld.)
Governor, it's right ahead.
I buried his head right here.
I'll trouble you soldiers
to dig it up yourselves.
Governor, shouldn't you give me...
You know.
Thank you.
Dig it up.
Don't forget.
It was I who taught you the Art of War.
The Governor expected this from you.
So he had me wait in the wings.
Go. Inform the Xiaosheng Society
that I've captured Xu You'an.
Make sure Rong Xiaonan hears it.
Mr. Du.
Mr. Rong, you've rested enough.
Can you take me
to find the Jade Buddha Head now?
Since I agreed to cooperate with you,
I will certainly do my best.
But...
Mr. Rong, say what you need to.
After all, we are friends.
Have you ever wondered
why the Buddha Head became a fake one
once it reached Xu Fan?
And why the crown went missing
once it passed through Xu Fan's hands?
Xu Fan has entrenched himself
in Fengcheng for decades.
He is extremely cunning
and ruthless.
Since Xu Fan had the ability
to retake the Governor Mansion,
then why did he let Xu You'an
run rampant for so long
and even allow your society
to be ransacked?
Mr. Rong, your tactic of sowing discord
is cleverly used.
I am indeed tempted.
But let me make it clear to you,
whoever helps me
find the Jade Buddha Head
is my friend.
Then I'm afraid you might only
be able to befriend me.
Sir,
Governor Mansion sent someone.
Let him in.
Yes.
What does Governor Xu want?
Mr. Du,
the Governor has captured
the traitor Xu You'an.
He invites you over to witness it.
Alright. I'll be there shortly.
Would you like to come along, Mr. Rong?
Of course.
Xu Fan is doing so as a warning to you.
I must be present for this good show.
If I were you,
I would protect Xu You'an.
Having someone who can restrain Xu Fan
will keep the cooperation balanced.
If he has no rivals left in Fengcheng,
then the next one
to be devoured entirely
will be you, Mr. Du.
Why should I believe you?
Mr. Du,
now everyone knows
I am your honored guest.
But once we get there,
Xu Fan will definitely kill Xu You'an.
He will also demand my death.
Because his trusted man
saw me and the phoenix crown
at your place together.
Once I am dead,
the Buddha Head will forever remain
in Xu Fan's territory.
I don't know what's exactly so good
about these two treasures
that you two are so obsessed with them.
But if these treasures
can bring benefits from somewhere,
then Xu Fan might prefer
to handle it himself,
rather than trouble you
with passing it through your hands.
(The past must eventually be faced)
Now we must find
the Buddha Head before them
to disrupt their cooperation.
This matter started
with Head Rong and your mother.
Look through your mother's belongings.
Maybe you can find some clues.
This photo doesn't look like
it's from the Rongqing Troupe.
It's from the old troupe that Mother
and Head Rong were in together.
Could the Jade Buddha Head
be hidden there?
You didn't expect it, huh?
I had sent people
to watch the Jiang residence closely.
Not a single move of yours
escaped my notice.
Right.
I heard Rong Xiaonan has become
the Xiaosheng Society's honored guest.
Xu You'an, being betrayed
doesn't feel pleasant, right?
Kill me if you want.
Stop wasting words.
I went to all this trouble
precisely to fulfill the bond
between you two brothers
of dying on the same day,
same month, and same year.
Speak of the devil.
Mr. Du. I heard this traitor
once offended you.
This is the Governor Mansion's
reply to you.
You're too kind, Governor Xu.
You know what I want most.
I don't care who lives or dies.
Mr. Du,
why does it sound like
you're not quite satisfied with me?
There must be someone sowing discord,
saying things they shouldn't.
I am Mr. Du's guest.
Governor Xu, by targeting me like this,
shouldn't you ask Mr. Du if he agrees?
As expected of an opera singer,
full of nonsense.
I am eliminating
a hidden danger for Mr. Du.
Your master died
at the hands of Mr. Du and me.
How could you not hate us?
Do you think I don't know?
You're doing this
to seek revenge, right?
Governor Xu, you're really funny.
My master died because of you
and that scoundrel Jiang Xiaoren.
Why are you so determined
to drag Mr. Du down with you?
You!
Enough.
I don't have time to watch you two
put on a show here.
Governor Xu, if you're sincere,
just hand Xu You'an over to me.
If you're not, then there's no need
to discuss cooperation further.
Don't touch me with your filthy hands!
Do you know what kind of path
you're walking now?
You're acting as an accomplice,
and that path ends in death.
Xu You'an,
we both have paths we must take.
The only thing I can do right now
is to follow Mr. Du.
Then I'd rather die
by the gun of a demon
than see you in such a filthy state now.
You've sunk low enough
to run with that crowd.
I tried to save you,
but I caused Yongnian's death.
Every time I think of
how Yongnian died in front of me,
I wish I could kill you.
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
If you want to die
for your foolish justice,
then I'll send you on your way.
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪